Guide to the Communist Party of the United States of America Audio Collection TAM.132.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series IV: Audio Cassette Tapes: Public Events
  - Subseries IV:A: Events
    - Marxist Forum on Homelessness and Unemployment. George Meyers, Lecture, Mar 17 (Box 52, Cassette 4060)
    - Hosea Hudson, Experiences of Black Workers and the Role of the CPUSA in the South. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], Mar 22 (Box 59, Cassette 952)
    - Communist Party Election Ticket, Interview / County-Level Party Organizers, Mar 25 (?) (Box 59, Cassette 1080)
    - Young Communist League Student Conference. Tape 2, Mar 28 (Box 55, Cassette 4161)
    - Young Communist League Student Conference. Tape 4, [Mar 28] (Box 55, Cassette 4162)
    - Philip Bart, [Party History], Mar 29 (Box 58, Cassette 1328)
    - Philip Bart, Party History. Tape 1, Mar 29 (Box 58, Cassette 1297)
    - Philip Bart, Party History. Tape 2, Mar 29 (Box 58, Cassette 1296)
    - John (?) Pittman, Anti-Communist Myths, Apr 14 (Box 55, Cassette 4100)
    - Daniel Rubin, Lecture on Political Economy, Apr 17 (Box 32, Cassette 4883)
    - Zach Schiller, Portland Alliance (?) and UAW, Apr 26 (Box 58, Cassette 1199)
    - Industrial Workers Conference. Tape 2, May 8 (Box 34, Cassette 1643)
    - Boleslaw (Bill) Gebert, George Siskind, Enla Mendes and James Papendrew, Interviewed by Beatrice Johnson, May 18-May 20 in Warsaw, Poland. Topics include 1930s Unemployed Struggles, CIO Organizing, New Bedford Textile Strike, Earl Browder, McCarthy Period, Party Financing. [Additional information on cassette container] (Box 58, Cassette 1295, Box 64, Cd 1295)
    - Unidentified [East Coast Party Building?] Conference. Gus Hall, May 26 or J__ 26 - J__ 27, 1973 (Box 36, Cassette 985)
    - National League School. Henry Winston, Sep 14 (Box 52, Cassette 4068)
    - Gus Hall, Discussing Iraq and the Bush Administration, Sep 25 (Box 32, Cassette 4803)
    - Gus Hall, Opening of the Marxist School. Unity Center, New York, NY, Oct 9 (Box 52, Cassette 4014)
    - Press Conference. ME, Oct 11 (Box 55, Cassette 4104)
    - Forum on the German Democratic Republic. Gus Hall, Lecture, Oct 26 (Box 52, Cassette 4008)
    - National Leadership Conference. James Steele, Leninist Concept of the Youth League. Tape 1, Nov 15 (Box 52, Cassette 4063)
    - National Leadership Conference. James Steele and Lou Diskin, Leninist Concept of the Youth League. Tape 2, Nov 15 (Box 52, Cassette 4064)
    - National Leadership School. Includes Lou Diskin. Tape 3, Nov 15 (Box 55, Cassette 4260)
    - Charlene Mitchell and Danny Rubin, Lecture, Nov 26 (Box 58, Cassette 1118)
    - [?] Rusin, Strategic Outlook of the CPUSA, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4115)
    - Aaron Queen, Artek Party, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1155)
    - African-American Equality Panel, undated (Box 30, Cassette 1503)
    - African-Americans in the Labor Movement. Includes Christopher Alstin, Sheldon Tapps and Lillian Hatcher. Detroit, MI, undated (Box 56, Cassette 4630)
    - Alliance of Racist Israel and South Africa / Sulan A., On Islam and Article by John Ali, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1254)
    - Alva Buxenbaum, [Marxism and Sex?]. Tape 2 [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], undated (Box 52, Cassette 4059)
    - Alva Buxenbaum, Teachers' Convention, undated (Box 52, Cassette 3979)
    - Angela Davis. Portland, OR. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], undated (Box 52, Cassette 3986)
    - Anne Burlak Timpson, Memoirs. Tape 2, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4140)
    - Anne Burlak Timpson, Memoirs. Tape 3, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4141)
    - Anti-Imperialism Conference. Tape 1, undated (Box 52, Cassette 3969)
    - Anti-Imperialism Conference. Tape 2, undated (Box 52, Cassette 3970)
    - Anti-Imperialism Conference. Tape 2, undated (Box 28, Cassette 1191)
    - Anti-Imperialism Conference. Tape 3, undated (Box 28, Cassette 1145)
    - Arnold Becchetti, Report on the 14th Italian Congress, undated (Box 52, Cassette 3975)
    - Arnold Johnson, College Audience. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], undated (Box 52, Cassette 4046)
    - Art Shields, Pamphlet (?), undated (Box 55, Cassette 4123)
    - Art Shields, Recruitment Speech, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4122)
    - Article in New York Times on Senior Citizens and Utilities / Statement of Eight Principles between the U.S. and Panama, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1210)
    - Barry Cohen, Introduction to Political Economy. Tape 10, undated (Box 52, Cassette 3983)
    - Barry Cohen, Introduction to Political Economy. Tape 11, undated (Box 52, Cassette 3984)
    - Barry Cohen, Introduction to Political Economy. Tape 9, undated (Box 52, Cassette 3982)
    - Beatrice Johnson, As I Think Back (Recollections of Party Organizing). Topics include 1927 Miners' Strike, Detroit, MI (1940-1941), War Time in Peoria IL (1942-1943), undated (Box 58, Cassette 1404)
    - Beatrice Johnson, As I Think Back (Recollections of Party Organizing). Topics include Culture to the Masses, 1941 Ford Strike. Tape 2, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1402)
    - Beatrice Johnson, As I Think Back (Recollections of Party Organizing). Topics include Miners' Unity in Southern Illinois, Mother Bloor, the Unemployed Movement and Women's Equality. Tape 1, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1403)
    - Beatrice Siskin, Recollections of Party History, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1405)
    - Betty Smith, History of the Communist Party 1959-1981. Tape 45, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4124)
    - Bill [Taylor], Interview, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1246)
    - Building the Young Communist League in High Schools, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4237)
    - Building the Young Communist League in the Community. Tape 1, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4238)
    - Building the Young Communist League in the Community. Tape 2, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4157)
    - Carl Winter, Developments in Colombia, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1279)
    - Carl Winter, Unidentified Lecture, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4879)
    - Charlene Mitchell, on the Wilmington 10 Victory, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4976)
    - Claude Lightfoot, Black Capitalism or Socialism, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4051)
    - Club Life Discussion. Tape 2, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4966)
    - Community Discussion Group, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4240)
    - Conference on the Ideological Problems of International Free Trade and How It Affects Mexico, Canada and the US. Includes Partido Popular Socialista (Mexico), the Communist Party of Canada and the CPUSA, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4083)
    - Conrad Komorowki, What's New in Poland. Tape 2, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4047)
    - Control Commission. Unidentified Response to Statement by Michael Meyerson, undated (Box 32, Cassette 5012)
    - Corruption in the Courts. Discussion of Court Case Involving General Motors and United Auto Workers Local 719, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4266)
    - Cuba Solidarity. Tape 2, undated (Box 65, Cd 4222, Box 55, Cassette 4222)
    - Daniel Rubin, Lecture on Capitalism, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4933)
    - Daniel Rubin, Lecture on the Young Communist League, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4909)
    - Daniel Rubin, Role of the Branches, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4977)
    - Danny Winston, Young Workers Liberation League (Reel 3), undated (Box 55, Cassette 4151)
    - Dave Lippman and George Shrub, Committee to Intervene Anywhere, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4052)
    - Debrief on AFL-CIO Week of Mobilization, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4858)
    - Democratic Centralism. Tape 2, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4275)
    - Democratic Centralism. Tape 3, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4278)
    - Discussion of Club Educationals, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4862)
    - Discussion of High School Recruitment, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4969)
    - Discussion of United States Constitution (?) / Music, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4142)
    - Discussion on Debray's Book (continued). Tape 2, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4031)
    - Discussion on Debray's Book. Includes James Jackson and Alberto Moreau. Tape 1, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4030)
    - Discussion on Energy Consumption (as a critque of the working class), undated (Box 32, Cassette 4852)
    - Discussion on Racism, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4970)
    - Discussion on Racism in the Music Profession, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1276)
    - Discussion on Recruitment and Fundraising in the National Office, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4881)
    - Discussion on the Importance of Ideology. Includes Victor Perlo, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4853)
    - Discussion on Trade Unionism. Tape 2, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4271)
    - Doctor Linda Murry, Health Worker in Illinois, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4062)
    - Documentary on Karl Marx, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4912)
    - Dorothy Healy, Statement Resigning from the Communist Party of the USA, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4941)
    - Dr. Helen Caldicott, Lecture *, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1298)
    - Draft Education Tape on White Chauvinism, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1202)
    - Editorials: Conscientious Objection to Military Service in the United States, and Changes in Marxist-Leninist Debate, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1258)
    - Education on White Chauvinism, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1168)
    - Erie Movement Conference (Successor to the Niagra Movement). Tape 1, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4910)
    - Erie Movement Conference (Successor to the Niagra Movement). Tape 2, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4911)
    - Fern Winston, Struggle for Women's Equality, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4145)
    - Forward March of Cuba, undated (Box 65, Cd 4248, Box 55, Cassette 4248)
    - Friendship of National Groups in Azerbaijan, Specific Focus on Karabakh, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1283)
    - George Meyers, Trade Union Participation in the Peace Movement, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4906)
    - Gil Green, Report on Political Situation in Spain, undated (Box 28, Cassette 1314)
    - Greek Youth Festival. Athens, Greece, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4004)
    - Gus Hall (?), undated (Box 55, Cassette 4205)
    - Gus Hall (?), Lecture on the Strength of the Communist Party, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4893)
    - Gus Hall and Carole Marks, Recruitment Meeting. New York District, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4012)
    - Gus Hall and Gil Green, Report on Peace Movement, undated (Box 59, Cassette 1027)
    - Gus Hall, Address to Staff of the People's Daily World. Tape 2, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4005)
    - Gus Hall, How Are Communists Different?, undated (Box 49, Cassette 3706)
    - Gus Hall, Maoism, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4009)
    - Gus Hall, New Dangers and Estimate of the Republican Convention, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4010)
    - Gus Hall, Overseas Call and Press Report, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4015)
    - Gus Hall, Recruitment Meeting. Unity Center, New York, NY, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4017)
    - Gus Hall, Reed University. Portland, OR, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4073)
    - Gus Hall, Score Card for Districts and National, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4020)
    - Gus Hall, Speech on Militarism, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4850)
    - Gus Hall, Speech on the McCarran Internal Security Act. Reed University, Portland, OR, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4018)
    - Gus Hall, Speech on Trade. Includes Questions and Answers, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4949)
    - Gus Hall, The F.B.I., undated (Box 52, Cassette 4021)
    - Gus Hall, Unidentified Speech, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4871)
    - [Gus Hall], Unidentified Speech, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4281)
    - Gus Hall, Visit to Cuba, undated (Box 65, Cd 4023, Box 52, Cassette 4023)
    - Gus Hall, Watergate and Anti-Communism. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], undated (Box 58, Cassette 1169)
    - Gus Hall, What’s New? Tape 2, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4024)
    - Gus Hall, White Chauvinism, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1156)
    - Gus Hall, World Revolutionary Struggle. Sessions 1 and 2. Tape 24, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4025)
    - Harry Gottlieb, Birthday, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4003)
    - Health Crisis, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1253)
    - Henry Winston (?), Speech, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4848)
    - Henry Winston / James Steele. Tape 10, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4150)
    - Henry Winston and Tony Monteiro. Tape 2, undated (Box 59, Cassette 1012)
    - Henry Winston Committee, Rogue Party of a New Type / Gus Hall, World Relations. Tape 22 [Note: Poor audio quality], undated (Box 52, Cassette 4026)
    - Henry Winston, Interview (for Unidentified Article), undated (Box 59, Cassette 1103)
    - Henry Winston, Lecture to Students on SALT II and Nuclear Disarmament, undated (Box 59, Cassette 1100)
    - Henry Winston, on the Party and Mass Movements, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4147)
    - Henry Winston, Pan-Africanism and Black Youth. Yale University, New Haven, CT. [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], undated (Box 58, Cassette 1265)
    - Henry Winston, Party Building / George Meyers, Apartheid, undated (Box 59, Cassette 1068)
    - Henry Winston, Speech. Yale University, New Haven, CT, undated (Box 59, Cassette 1001)
    - Henry Winston, Studs Terkel and Mike Royko, Speeches, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1218)
    - Henry Winston, Summary, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4152)
    - Henry Winston, Summary [of Discussion on Party Building in Shops], undated (Box 59, Cassette 1005)
    - Henry Winston, Unidentified Speech. Tape 6 [Note: Poor audio quality], undated (Box 32, Cassette 4922)
    - [Henry Winston Committee?], Rogue Party of a New Type / Danny Rubin, Strategy and Tactics. Tape 27, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4114)
    - Herbert Aptheker, Defeating Reaction. John Reed Bookstore, Portland, OR, undated (Box 52, Cassette 3971)
    - Herschel Walker, Personal History of Organizing in the Communist Party, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1387)
    - History Makers, Lenin, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4029)
    - Hosea Hudson, Organizing the Masses, undated (Box 59, Cassette 953)
    - Hyman Lumer, Lecture on Zionism. Tape 1, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1338)
    - Hyman Lumer, Lecture on Zionism. Tape 2, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1337)
    - Hyman Lumer, Lecture. Gosmer College, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4054)
    - Hyman Lumer, Zionism, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4055)
    - Industrial Workers Conference. Tape 1, undated (Box 34, Cassette 1678)
    - Interview Concerning Attacks on Elijah Muhammad the Nation of Islam, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1235)
    - Interview on the Treatment of Jews in the Soviet Union [English and Russian language], undated (Box 55, Cassette 4105)
    - Introduction to Marxism-Leninism. Tape 1, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4255)
    - Introduction to Marxism-Leninism. Tape 2, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4253)
    - Introduction to Marxism-Leninism. Tape 3, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4254)
    - Irving Potash, Interview, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4841)
    - Jack Kling, Questions on Israel, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1324)
    - Jack Kling, Reflections on Convention Speeches, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1270)
    - James Jackson, Joe Henderson Banquet. Baltimore, MD, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4035)
    - James Jackson, Maoism. Tape 2, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4036)
    - James Jackson, National Question, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4039)
    - James Jackson, National Question / Tommy Dennis, Afro-American Liberation. Tape 38, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4038)
    - James Jackson, National Question. Tape 37, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4037)
    - James Jackson, on Capitalism. Lecture 3 in a Series of 5, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4040)
    - James Jackson, on Masoism, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4974)
    - James Jackson, on Socialism. Lecture 4 in a Series of 5, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4042)
    - James Jackson, on the Communist Party, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4041)
    - James Jackson, on the Nationality Question and Discussion, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1317)
    - James Steele, Conversation, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4133)
    - James Steele, Keynote Address. Also Includes Gus Hall and [Antar] Mberi, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4134)
    - James Steele, on Evaluation, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4959)
    - James Steele, on Youth Mobilization. Tape 2, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4961)
    - James Tormey, Resolution, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1119)
    - Jarvis Tyner, African-American Equality, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4139)
    - Jarvis Tyner, Lecture. Detroit, MI, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4868)
    - Jarvis Tyner, Transit / George Meyers, Public Workers, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4866)
    - Jarvis Tyner. Tape 1, undated (Box 59, Cassette 863)
    - Jay [Schaffner?], Youth Question. Tape 4, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1176)
    - Jewish Affairs Dinner, 12th Annual. Tape 2, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4957)
    - Jewish Affairs Dinner. Includes Herbert Aptheker and [?] Ehrlich. Tape 2, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4045)
    - Jewish Affairs Dinner. Speaker from the ANC. Tape 1, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4044)
    - Jim Badger, Comedy and Poetry Reading at Young Communist League, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4156)
    - Jim West, Ideological Discussion, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4144)
    - Jim West, Speech, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1234)
    - Jarvis Tyner, African-American Equality, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4138)
    - Joe Brandt, Lecture on Maoism, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4901)
    - John Abt Dinner. Includes Joe Forer, Judge Wright, Carole Gerstl, Bonnie Brown and Gus Hall, undated (Box 52, Cassette 3967)
    - John and Evelyn Vafiades, On the Akron, OH Rubber Strike and Agitation in the 1930s. Tape 2, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1363)
    - Judith Le Blanc, All-Youth Front, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4049)
    - Judy Simmions (?), The Woman Question, undated (Box 59, Cassette 910)
    - [Karen] Talbot, Building an International Peace Movement and Independent Force, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1143)
    - Kenneth Neill Cameron, Lecture on Joseph Stalin, undated (Box 52, Cassette 3980)
    - Kenneth Neill Cameron, Lecture on Joseph Stalin. [Tape 2?], undated (Box 52, Cassette 3981)
    - Labor Department, Discussion. Tape 2, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4257)
    - Labor Department, Discussion. Tape 3, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4258)
    - Lawyers Discussing the Defense of Angela Davis, undated (Box 44, Cassette 2565)
    - Lecture on Progressive Legislation. Tape 1, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4982)
    - Lecture on Progressive Legislation. Tape 2, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4983)
    - Lecture on the Industrial Worker in the Class Struggle, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4861)
    - Lecture, On Capitalism and Exchange, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1260)
    - Len Levenson, Interview. Side 3, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1288)
    - Lerone Bennett, Jr., Ebony Magazine. Tape 1, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1247)
    - Limitations of Non-Working Class Forces in the Struggle for Human Progess, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4815)
    - Lou Diskin, Social Democracy. Tape 26, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4884)
    - Lou Diskin, What is Marxism?, undated (Box 52, Cassette 3991)
    - Louise Patterson, Message from William L. Patterson, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1413, Box 64, Cd 1413 (disks 1-2))
    - Marxism and Sex. Tape 1 [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], undated (Box 52, Cassette 4057)
    - Marxism and Sex. Tape 2 [Condition poor: creation of user copy may pose problems. Contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu], undated (Box 52, Cassette 4058)
    - Mary Licht, Lecture on Communist Party History from 1939, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1289)
    - Michael Zagarell, Education in the League; Matty Berkelhammer, Organization in the League. Tape 4 (?), undated (Box 55, Cassette 4168)
    - Michael Zagarell, The Phony Left, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4169)
    - Morton High School Interview, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4028)
    - National [League] School. Building the Young Workers Liberation League, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4065)
    - National League School. Building the Branches, Discussion, Report Backs and Evaluation, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4066)
    - National League School. Danny Spector, Building the Young Workers Liberation League. Lecture and Discussion (Day 6), undated (Box 52, Cassette 4076)
    - National League School. Evaluation (continued), undated (Box 52, Cassette 4067)
    - National League School. George Meyers, the Fight against Racism. Lecture and Discussion, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4071)
    - National League School. Keta Miranda, Building the League. Also includes Gus Hall. Tape 5, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4072)
    - National League School. Larry Moskowitz / Discussion on Organization of the Young Workers Liberation League (Day 5), undated (Box 52, Cassette 4075)
    - National League School. Lou Diskin, Socialism and Today's Youth / Keta Miranda, Building the League. Tape 4, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4070)
    - National League School. Lou Diskin, Socialism and Today's Youth. Tape 3, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4069)
    - National League School. Without Revolutionary Theory, Discussion, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4078)
    - National League School. Without Revolutionary Theory, Discussion. Tape 2, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4077)
    - [National Party] School. Discussion on Struggle against Racism in the CPUSA, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1267)
    - Nitty Gritty Club Meeting, undated (Box 28, Cassette 1211)
    - Nitty Gritty Club Meeting. Critique of "The Meaning of San Rafael", undated (Box 28, Cassette 1123)
    - Nitty Gritty Club Meeting. Critique of "The Meaning of San Rafael." [2], undated (Box 28, Cassette 1203)
    - On the Rosenberg Case. Carnegie Hall, New York, NY, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4111)
    - On the Upsurge of the Labor and Anti-Imperialist Movement (?). Tape 13, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4872)
    - Panel Discussion, Building the League. Includes James Steele, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4265)
    - Party Board, Youth Meeting, undated (Box 44, Cassette 2654)
    - Party Roundtable on Labor, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4225)
    - Paul Robeson, on Civil Rights, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4107)
    - Paul Robeson, Political Speeches, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4108)
    - People's Fightback Rally. Includes Gus Hall, Angela Davis and James Steele. Cobo Hall, Detroit, MI, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4218)
    - People's New Agenda Rally. Includes Scott Marshall, and Alderman Danny Davis. Chicago, IL. Tape 1, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4216)
    - People's New Agenda Rally. Includes Scott Marshall, and Alderman Danny Davis. Chicago, IL. Tape 2, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4217)
    - People's School Graduation Ceremony. Includes Henry Winston, undated (Box 32, Cassette 4869)
    - Philip Bart, History of the Communist Party. Tape 35, undated (Box 52, Cassette 3973)
    - Police Brutality Workshop, Education, Clarification and Proposals. Tape 3, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4103)
    - Police Brutality Workshop, Education. Tape 2, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4102)
    - Police Brutality Workshop. Tape 1, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4101)
    - Political Affairs Forum on Culture. Michael Parenti, Lecture, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4079)
    - Political Affairs Forum. Angela Davis, undated (Box 52, Cassette 3987)
    - Political Affairs Forum. Gus Hall, Class Unity and Class Consciousness, undated (Box 52, Cassette 4006)
    - Rally against Reaganism. Includes Gus Hall, Angela Davis and James Steele, undated (Box 55, Cassette 4220)
    - Rally for Jobs. Washington, DC *, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1174)
    - Raymond Mosely, Interview, undated (Box 58, Cassette 1139)
    - Reading of Article "Immigrant Votes Proposed for LA School Board", undated (Box 32, Cassette 4890)